Do you want subtitles for any video?
-=[ ai.OpenSubtitles.com ]=-
Yes. Mr. Cho.
Yes. that's the place.
The warehouse where we
worked on the Japanese kid.
Yes. he's comfy and well.
He was a lot gentler than what you told me.
He wasn't trouble at all.
he took my lead well.
He was a bit cheeky though.
He's a funny guy.
How much was this guy worth by the way?
Right? I knew he was loaded.
He's covered in designer goods.
What?
Oh...
He must be rich.
Yes. I see.
We got a proper merchandise for once.
Almost here? I left the door open.
Come on right in.
I'll see...
Fucker. I was talking...
Mr. Cho's almost here.
Get out!
Get out now!
Shit!
Fuck...
It's been a while. friend.
I told you. you'd see me again soon.
You... wait...
It's just...
Oh yeah. I said I'd give you money.
I'll give it to you for real!
I'm not lying this time.
you'll get it. okay?
It's fine.
Friends shouldn't pay each other money.
Don't kill me! Please don't kill me!
Goddammit. what are you doing?!
You got blood on my shoe!
Motherfucker!
Asshole.
it's this season's brand new model!
I barely managed to buy it
from the first batch!
I could just fucking kill you!
Look at it.
I'm going to use this
to carve your heart out.
You know what?
Blunt instruments are more painful
than sharp knives.
You can't die quickly with these.
How much is your client paying you?
I'll pay you double...
Friend. you said we're friends!
Don't kill me. please!
Right. friend.
I told you.
I'm the last friend you'll meet
before you die.
It's nothing personal.
We're pros. and this is just business.
THE CHILDE
Executive Producer KIM WOO-TAEK
Produced by PARK HOON-JUNG
Written & Directed by PARK HOON-JUNG
Nice work today. Marco.
You promised me more
from this match onwards.
Hey. Marco!
You eat well and take care
of yourself with that money!
You know about the big match
next week. right?
I put a shit load of money on you!
Arrogant bastard...
Fucking Kopino half-breed...!
Got your butt kicked this time?
Your opponent was a Thai?
Those Thais sure got spicy punches.
Someone really did a number
on our mighty Marco's face.
Don't glare at me. idiot.
How's your mother?
She should really get that surgery soon.
What brings you here today?
Because of your father?
Any news?
Nothing so far.
But hang in there.
If he's alive. you might find him one day.
I wouldn't even be looking for that man
if it wasn't for Mom's operation.
Come on now.
What's that?
Use it to hire someone in
Korea to look for him.
Hey! Hey!
Marco!
You're later than usual.
LaLiga's it's closed already
but Premier League is still betting.
Which team has the highest odds?
Let's see...
Um. Burnley?
Yeah. it's Burnley.
They're going against Chelsea.
What are the odds?
250 to 1.
All on Burnley.
Hey Marco.
that's not a great idea.
Why don't you just buy the lotto ticket?
You a lot of better chance at winning.
I said all on Burnley.
Whatever.
It's on me. mate.
Long time no see. Marco.
That last fight was fucking sick. huh?
Big shot Thai guy didn't
fucking stand a chance.
Thanks to you... I made a pretty penny.
Um? thanks for that...
Oh yeah. So ah...
how's searching for daddy going?
Any leads?
Of course not...
What do you care?
But I do have a job that
might interest you.
I've had my eye on this
fancy jewelry store downtown.
I'm gonna get to work on it... You want in?
Come on. man.
All you have to do is cut the power
and keep the security busy.
You don't even have to go in
and I'll give you 10%.
Store that size...
even with the middleman
it'll be 100 big ones. easy.
10% Marco...
What do you say?
I'll think about it.
Come on. man. Fuck!
What's there to think about?
You know what.
I'll even forget about mommy's medication.
Chelsea 4:0
Yo. Chelsea took all your money.
When you go around the back to the building
you'll find the power box
and a guard booth.
Here.
They'll bust in as soon as you
keep the guards to busy.
cut the power to the building.
No problem.
Get back fuckers!
Hey! Are you okay?!
Oh no. are you okay?
I didn't see you run out...
We should go to the hospital...
Why am I speaking Korean?
I'm really sorry.
We should go to a hospital right away.
Korean?
- Are you Korean? - What?
Well. not exactly.
How are you feeling?
All the tests came back well.
I told you this was unnecessary.
we could've settled last night.
what was the point of this?
Even so. you just never know
with accidents.
There could be lasting effects.
This isn't much. please take it.
and I'm so sorry.
By the way. you speak Korean really well.
You look like one too.
anyone will think that you're a Korean.
I get that a lot.
Did you learn Korean somewhere?
Or are you...
what was it called?
Kopino?
You are Kopino. right?
Sorry. I shouldn't have said that...
Yeah?
What?
I was gonna take your money.
but it stank so badly of your sweat.
It'd be proper to say that
they were looking for us.
rather than us looking for them.
It means your father
did not forget about you.
As you know. cases like this are so rare.
How many fathers came looking
for their Kopino kids here?
None. zero.
They just plant their seeds
and get the hell out of here.
When is he coming?
Oh yeah. he's coming right away.
It looked like he was in a hurry.
And this is my gift to you.
It's a Korean calling card.
You might need it there.
so keep it with you.
What a stench.
Marco Han?
You're him.
Good to meet you.
Thank you.
Law Firm The Royal Partner Kang Won-seok
Your father's a bit sick.
so I came instead.
Do you understand what I just said?
I don't speak Tagalog at all.
but a little English.
would you prefer that?
It's okay. you can speak Korean.
You speak Korean so well.
Mom forced me to speak Korean or English.
I had to go to a Korean school.
Korean school?
You need those to fly.
Passport. visa and such.
Isn't money great?
Anything is solvable with it.
Han. look here.
She's a hospice nurse who
will look after your mother.
Because of your father's condition.
we have to hurry.
Pack lightly and come out.
Right now?
Why? ls there a problem?
But...
For her sake.
wouldn't it be best to head out ASAP?
Paying for her surgery is not
even a bother to him.
He'll take care of it right away.
It's a quick flight to Seoul.
Pack up quickly. okay?
He really wants to see you.
Hokyung Foundation Accused of Slush Fund...
Illegal Succession at Hokyung Foundation...
Hokyung Foundation's Slush Fund
Whistleblowers Missing...
Attorney Kang Won-seok
Yes. Kang. how did it go?
Very good. that's great.
When's the flight?
Okay.
I'll have everyone on standby.
come here at once.
Okay. good.
So? How did it go?
Sir?
Thankfully.
their editors are quite amicable to us.
so we managed to kill all articles.
Return for what?
We will be the main sponsor
for Daeil Daily's annual
corporation expo for the next 3 years.
For the other 3 outlets.
we'll be the main ad client...
So pathetic...
It's so easy taking someone else's money.
It's a sensitive period.
it'd be best not to get mixed up
with malicious tabloids.
I know.
Do I look like a moron
who can't read the room?
That's not what I meant.
Whatever.
Sir?
That'll be all.
Yes. sir.
You haven't been here in a long time.
Get some rest and see you tomorrow.
That's all right. sir.
I'll head back to Seoul...
As you wish. sir.
There's someone I want you to meet.
so let's have breakfast tomorrow.
Yes. sir.
This way.
So. Father. how are you holding up?
They're leaving the Philippines.
so just hang in there.
What did you say?
Yes. Father. the youngest.
That youngest son you've been
waiting for is on the way.
Happy?
Are you?
Yes. that mutt.
Your mutt's on the way here.
Just hang on until he arrives. okay?
We don't have time.
Have cars on standby so that
we can leave immediately.
Understood. sir.
Man. I almost missed it.
I thought you'd leave tomorrow.
but returning on the same day?
They must really be in a hurry.
They're filthy rich.
putting you in business class?
Who am I?
A friend.
Consider me a friend for now.
Listen. friend.
You're heading to Korea.
do you even know why you're going?
What?
There's no way you would.
Oh yeah.
isn't this your first time in Korea?
Should I give you a tip?
This will help you out big time.
Once you're there.
use English whenever possible.
Koreans fucking love
English speaking people.
Hey this works. For sure.
One hundred percent.
And of course.
an American accent is the best.
Pretend like a 2nd.
or 3rd generation Korean-American.
Trust me.
They'll fucking lick your balls...
A British accent is OK too.
but Koreans aren't really used to it.
So an American accent is the best.
works every time.
Hey...
But don't use Southeast Asian accent.
Never. ever!
Better off not using it in that case.
gotta be careful.
No point in tipping off
that you're a Kopino.
Am I right?
Who the fuck are you?
Like I said. an amigo. a friend.
I may be the last friend in your life.
What?
By the way...
if we go by age. I'm actually older.
I look young but I got a few years on you.
So. you shouldn't swear
just because we're friends.
I really hate rude mofos.
What the fuck are you on about?
Who said I was gonna be your friend?
Life never works out the way
you intended. bud.
Your English pronunciation is quite good.
What the fuck are you talking about...!
Excuse me.
May I ask you to return to your seat?
- Of course. - Thank you.
Think about it.
Isn't it fishy?
Going to another country on a plane
isn't like walking to a local bar
to see your bookie.
Visa. passport and all that.
It's weird. don't you think?
Should I tell you why
you're going to Korea?
I'm off.
See you soon.
Crazy fuck...!
Yeah. we just touched down.
No. I'm on a delivery run.
Where are you?
Me? I'm in a business meeting.
Yeah.
How did you return so quickly
after the clean up?
Don't worry.
I did everything as per my order.
I cleaned it up nicely.
We were never there.
So my job's finished?
There's no end to our work.
Is he the one?
Yeah.
Put him inside.
Damn. my brother's hot.
Doesn't he look similar to a celeb?
Take a look.
So similar. right?
Who?
Right. you don't watch TV.
Too bad. that guy's hot too.
Look at his muscles. those are so dope.
Dope AF.
Yeah?
So? What will you do?
Do what?
Just stick to the original order.
Okay.
By the way...
what about the favor I asked you?
I brought it.
but do you really need it?
You never know.
I'm preparing for the worst.
Better safe than sorry.
Don't worry. I practiced a lot.
Shit. I'm gonna be late for school.
Yoon-ju. I have to go.
Thank you!
See you later!
It sure is stunning here.
Great water. great air...
Director Han. sir.
why are you doing this to me?
Director Han! What's going on?!
You are making a huge mistake!
You know who I am!
How will you handle the backlash...
That's enough.
Please keep your mouths shut.
your breath stinks.
So. you two are well acquainted?
No need to play dumb.
You're not just well acquainted.
you gents are practically BFFs.
Even so. this is plain nasty.
You hold great authority
and honor in this society.
Am I right. Mr. Publisher?
Hokyung Foundation Accused of Slush Fund...
Illegal Succession at Hokyung Foundation...
You have no problem sucking others dry.
what are you?
A tick or a parasite?
You fed him this shit. right?
Hokyung in Hot Waters Over Slush Fund...
I'm an impatient type.
could you answer right away?
Yes. yes!
How many years have you
worked with my father?
19 years? 20?
This is why I have
trust issues with humans.
You've swapped allegiance to Jang
after backstabbing my father?
Director Han. that's not it.
please listen to me.
Please. just this once.
I have to tell you something...
You think Jang will win?
Isn't that why you did this?
Director Han. please hear me out!
Please listen to me.
I got something to tell you...
You were here when this was built. no?
This is about 2.8 million sq ft. right?
Cedar forest over there.
and there. what's that tree?
Cypress tree. sir.
Right. cypress tree.
And even more forests beyond that.
There's not a single soul
within 10 km radius.
Aren't you curious?
These missing people.
where could they have gone?
Isn't that why you wrote it?
They're all here.
Director Han. please don't kill me!
Please. don't kill me!
What? What?
Sensitive period. right?
Don't worry about your family.
I sent all those photos to your families.
Every single one.
Not just to your wives.
but to all your children too.
So. don't you worry.
That's not all.
those are plastered all over the internet.
Both of you have disappeared.
leaving behind a will.
No one will find you. right?
Why'd anyone look for you.
after seeing these?
Untie him. right now!
Director Han. I'll do my best!
Sir. please!
Look at you.
For old time sake. I'll give you a chance.
See that forest over there?
The cedar forest.
If you reach there. I'll let you live.
Good? Let's run. are you ready?
One sec! Hold on!
Run in a zigzag.
You'll have lower chance of getting shot.
Thank you.
What are you doing. get ready.
Start running at 3.
I'll start shooting after 10.
Here we go.
One.
Two.
I said to run after 3.
he couldn't listen to save himself.
Dr. Lee. have you slept well?
Yes. thanks to you.
Have you heard?
Yes.
Everything is perfect. isn't it?
Please don't disappoint me this time.
It's almost time. please go prep.
Kid. how old are you?
Punk. I just asked you a question.
How old are you. asshole?
Twenty four.
Speak Korean. I know you speak it.
What an ignorant bastard.
You don't even know the basics?
He said 24.
Oh. 24.
Learn basic English. will you?
Learning it won't kill you.
Sure.
So full of vitality.
a long way from expiration date.
Shut your damn mouth and stick to driving!
Yes. sir.
What's that?
Why isn't he overtaking me
if he's so damn busy?
What the fuck?
Increase speed.
What the hell for?
Buddy!Hey!
You sure drive like a retard! Stop the car!
Step on it! Now!
Unknown Caller ID
Who is this?
What?
$0?
Who are you guys?
What?
How much?
Hey.
Get everyone on standby.
Marco!
Mercedes really is the shit.
It's worth every penny.
Hey friend. good to see you.
I told you we'd see each other soon.
There's a reason why people
go nuts over Mercedes.
If you get into an accident
like that without seat belts.
everyone should be dead.
Am I right?
Friend. are you scared?
There's no need to be. relax. ease up.
What are you looking at?
Thinking of taking off?
That won't be easy.
Who are you?
Tell me.
I told you. a friend.
- A friend? - Yes. that's right.
And this is... my job.
Why are you doing this to me?
It's a bit tough to explain
everything to you right now.
But don't worry.
You'll find out for yourself
when it's time for you to die.
What?
I told you in the airplane.
that you came here to die.
You're going there to die.
Fuck your shit. asshole.
Fuck... what?
Buddy! Where you going?!
He speaks Korean so well.
Hey!Buddy!
Stop! Hey!
It's a lot higher than I thought.
You okay?
Asshole. you got a death wish?
You son of a bitch!
Get over here. you fucking shit!
Shut your mouth.
Christ...
Dammit!
Huh? Very nice. that's great.
Director. we found it.
Professional?
Fucking bastards...
Father. looks like we got
a proper roadblock.
We got some hyenas around.
I don't know who these guys are.
but they're going all out.
Since you're down. they think we're weak.
and ambushing us. sons of bitches.
He wants $10 million.
He wants $10 million for that mutt.
It's all ready. sir.
Okay.
Just hang in there.
I'll go get that mutt myself.
Hello. this is Law Firm The Royal.
Please stay on the line.
we'll connect you right away.
Call Forwarding
- Hello? - Hello?
Seriously? That could've been terrible.
Where are you now?
Yes. I know where that is.
I'm on my way. so stay right there.
Mr. Kim. it's Marco!
Where are you?
I'm getting calls saying you disappeared!
Someone's trying to kill me.
What?
Everyone I came with are all dead!
What the hell are you saying?
Have you contacted your father?
You punk.
Stupid bastard.
Hey. friend!
Didn't I tell you that I've
never missed my targets?
This village is the only place
you could've run to from there.
it's too obvious!
I knew you'd be making
a call from the payphone!
How did I know?
I'm a professional.
An expert.
Stop. that's enough.
I said stop.
If you continue being uncooperative.
I could just shoot you dead.
No need to raise your hands though.
Right. he boxed...
Shit...
He's got a mean punch.
Proper hit could've killed me.
HOD in!
Man. oh. man...
It's a brand new car!
Fucking hell...
What's going on? What is happening here?
It's exactly as you see it.
So. do you remember me?
Are you okay?!
I didn't see you run out...
Kopino?
You are Kopino. right?
Who are you?
Who are you people?
Don't rush it.
you'll find out before you die.
What?
This will be fun.
The fuck's matter with him?
Turn it around! Now!
Why are they together? Go after them!
Where are we going?
To your father.
You came to Korea to see him. no?
The one following us is your brother.
He's the one who ordered
us to bring you in.
Speak of the devil.
What do you think you're doing?
Are you messing with me?
I don't really have the time
to mess around with you.
What?!
Then what are you doing right now?
Doing what? I'm carrying out my work.
Have you forgotten my order
of bringing that mutt?
Go nag Mr. Kang about it.
You ordered him. not me.
What?
I've told you several times already.
we may share the office.
but we're separate entities.
Are you insa...
Are you so desperate to die?
If you got the chops.
give it your best shot.
Hello? Hello?!
That fucking bitch!
Catch up to them.
Hold on tight.
Stay on them! Go!
Turn it around. asshole!
That bitch. let's move!
Catch up! Floor it!
Fucking morons. do they know how to drive?
What a fucking hassle.
Who's that in the Mercedes?
Holy shit. I almost died!
Jesus Christ...
Where did she go?
I'm asking you. asshole! Where is she?!
He's pretty good.
Father?
I thought we were going to him.
Your father?
He's nearby.
In this land of beautiful mountain.
water and air.
he's got maybe a day or two.
What's with that face?
Kang didn't tell you?
You father. Chairman Han is dying.
Bad heart. I hear.
He's the chairman of Seoul's
biggest foundation. did you know?
Hokyung Foundation built many
colleges in and around Seoul.
tons of hospitals too.
It's a huge foundation.
You didn't know it was that big?
I bet you thought your father
had a bit of money.
If it stopped right here.
you'd be the luckiest kid.
That's too bad. right?
He wouldn't have looked for you
if it stopped right here.
Your brother and your father
are in a bit of a rush.
If your father dies.
your brother'll lose the foundation
to his half-sister.
When the chairman was in
and out of consciousness.
his wife Jang got his will.
seal and vocal confirmation.
So. your brother has to keep him alive
- no matter what. - What the hell is this?!
I don't believe this...
That's why you're here. do you understand?
I don't...
The man you call your father
has really bad heart.
Your father and your brother...
need this. they need your heart.
You get it now?
What? Got more questions?
Me? I received the opposite order.
Wow. not bad at all.
Just stick to the original order.
Here or there. your fate is to die.
Think of it as clocking out slightly early.
What the fuck!
You fucking bastard!
My fucking car!
I'm gonna fucking kill her!
That's enough.
You messed up my car royally.
Fuck...
Stop running. it's hot.
I'm your big brother...
I'm happy to meet you.
My brother...
Come in. come in.
Think of this place as your own home. okay?
But why are you so dirty?
Let's go upstairs. come.
Do you like the place?
Follow me.
Oh my. Ga-young. when did you get here?
What a good kid.
you heard it's father's surgery day.
and got here just in time.
She's a good daughter.
You really have your ways.
You finally found this mutt.
Of course. watch your mouth though.
This is a matter of our
father's life and death.
Have you ever seen me fail?
Never. you're just that good.
Males in this household
don't do shit for my life.
You look like death.
Little sis.
if you need some allowance from me.
you and your mommy should be nice to me.
Fucking bitch.
Like mother. like daughter.
Try to understand her.
Our little sister was always a bitch.
Never mind that.
shall we go meet our father?
Let's go.
Father. your little boy is here.
Fuck...
Your call cannot be connected...
Recent Calls
So? What does it feel like to see him?
He's much too old for you and
Ga-young to call him father.
More like grandfather.
Come here.
This will be the first and last time.
all men in our family got together.
let's take a selfie to commemorate.
Smile. asshole. come on!
Smile!
That looks good.
What are you all doing? Let's get started.
What? You looked for him.
So why?
Not your type?
Be a good son.
How long will this take?
Dr. Lee says it will be about 9 hours.
We don't know what they're up to.
so put more men outside.
Yes. sir.
Marco!
The donor is conscious!
What? How is that possible?
Did you anesthetize him properly?
- Do it again! - Yes. doctor!
- Do it quickly! - Yes...
Doctor!
Check on the chairman first!
Get up. you awake?
It's me. friend.
So happy to see me?
We don't have a lot of time.
Could you snap out of it and get up?
One. two. three!
You punk.
Don't run around naked. put this on.
Motherfuckers...
Are you...
my father?
How could...
How could a father ask his son to
give up his heart so he can live?!
How could a father do that?!
If this is what you wanted...
you shouldn't have looked for me!
We don't have much time. wrap it up.
I've fucking had it...
That fucking mutt cannot die. got that?!
Yes. sir!
Move out of the fucking way!
Buddy!
Do you hear me?
Shit. answer me!
Answer me if you do. fucker!
Yeah. yeah. yeah. I hear you
very fucking well! Speak!
What's with that piss ass English?
- Just speak Korean. moron. - Piss ass...
I don't know who you are.
but let's come to an agreement.
Are you the one who asked for $10 million?
I am. fucker!
What will you do now?
What else?
Walk out of here.
We'll go out that door proudly.
Take the lead.
Never seen him before.
Give me a calculator.
1.10.100.1.000...
Do you even know how much
$10 million is in Korean won?
Of course.
At this morning's exchange rate.
it's 11.8575 billion won.
Very precise.
That is an incredible amount of money.
It's tough to get that kind of
money exchanged so quickly.
Don't worry. I can wait.
I got a lot of time today.
Okay. very well.
I'll meet you half way at $5 million.
Isn't that enough for that mutt?
Do you want half of this mutt's heart then?
$10 million.
- You're hard to bargain with.
- Firm price.
You could really screw yourself over.
Don't worry. I can handle myself.
That fucker...
All right. $7 million.
not a penny more. got it?
No. $10 million.
Front sight between rear sight...
- My offer is more than fair!
- Pull back the hammer.
Pull the trigger.
Stop! Stop shooting!
Are you out of your goddamn minds?!
That fucking bitch. is she nuts?!
You fucking assholes.
I told you not to shoot!
What's this?
Get in there and assess the situation!
Shit. I got hit...
No fucking way.
It was grazed by a bullet.
I can't get $10 million if he dies.
I was just saying.
don't look at me like that.
Seriously?
Bring the doctors back. you hear me?
Director Han. sir...
Friend. stay alert.
What? You sons of bitches!
You fucker...
Easy. easy. calm down.
why are you all worked up?
Your old man won't die right away.
And you guys are the ones
who shot him. not me.
What the fuck are you doing?!
So? Thanks to you. time's running out.
Son of a...
$10 million? You poor ass fuck.
Yeah. $10 million. you rich ass fuck.
Cayman Islands or Virgin Islands?
What?
Secret US dollar accounts you stashed away.
We did our homework.
Whichever is easier. which one?
- Caymans. - Okay.
Here. show your brother this.
Send it here right away.
Give me my phone.
It's me. send $10 million
to an account I tell you.
Yes. right away!
$10 million! In USD! Are you fucking deaf?!
United States dollar!
What?
Purpose? I made that account
so that I don't have to report!
It's my fucking money! You fucking bitch!
Give me another phone.
Screen's off. asshole. tap on it.
It's me.
Deposit Information: $10.000.000
Happy. asshole?
Put that gun down and hand over the mutt.
Okay. very well. that was the deal.
Take him.
Move. get a fucking move on!
Move. out of the way.
Father! You can't die!
Get him to the doctors now!
What?
Get over here. you shit. take him away!
Yo. friend!
Cheer up.
You're not dying today.
Don't worry. just trust me.
I'll be off then.
Shit...
I got hit in the leg...
I'll put your money to good use.
Think of it as doing a good deed.
Yo. poor ass fuck. stop.
What is it?
Killing me won't get you back your money.
I know. asshole.
I'll consider it as cost of doing business.
Why then?
It's rather embarrassing.
A rumor could get out that I got
robbed to a bunch of nobodies.
That's how the world works.
One con leads to another.
and I'll be a laughing stock.
Could you think it over?
Being embarrassed would be a better option.
Than being dead.
So full of shit until the end.
Buddy. can't you read the room?
I've said it many times.
I'm a professional.
What? Professional?
Get down!
Get down on the floor!
Easy. easy...
Professional...
Indeed.
You live hard for a poor ass fuck.
Is your flight coming up soon?
I'm too fucked up to walk you out.
Oh yeah. I...
Shit. I forgot about this.
This fucking hurts.
It hurts so much.
I completely forgot about it.
It's all over. so let's go home.
Don't worry about him.
he's got nothing to do with you.
Let's just go.
Hold me softly. asshole.
You saw who I am. right?
That hurts. easy...
Wait. wait...
Come out. I can see your shadow.
What the hell?
This isn't even funny.
Do you see this?
I'll let it slide this time.
just move aside. okay?
You can go. I don't need you.
The game's over. Missy.
Your father's fortune's all yours.
that must be nice.
Congratulations. good.
Go have a party with your mom.
and move aside.
We're busy.
You boys took me for a fool?
Was I that obvious?
What if that mutt comes back
and changes his story?
Saying he's part of this family.
or spilling the beans about
what happened today.
What if he blackmail us later?
What a headache.
Why? Did I sting you in the feels?
No. no...
Fucking bastard.
Do I look like a panhandler?
I won't take your dirty money
even if you fed it to me. got it?
You fucking nobody.
you expect me to believe you?
I'd rather trust my dog.
And you!
What? Me? Really?
You called me?
How much? I'll hire you.
How much do you want to
get rid of this mutt?
Under the circumstances.
the minimum fee is...
What the hell am I saying?
Why are all offspring of
this family so fucked up?
Is it the blood?
Consider yourself lucky that
you didn't get that blood.
Don't make that face like
it's a big revelation.
I told you just a moment ago.
You got nothing to do with these people.
You know most of fixers
in the Philippines. right?
Find a kid for me. it's a rush job.
The client could die in a day or two.
Just find him. you'll get a fat check.
Say what?
Get me a decent guy.
You need money to save
this place and build a school.
But even so...
If this place disappears.
what'll happen to them?
Will you let them roam
the alleys like we did?
Those fuckers want a
child's heart so they can live.
What's your hang up?
That's why get me a
mentally tough and smart guy.
By the way...
don't you trust me? What's with you?
I'm a professional.
I got a decent reputation
in my line of work.
You know that.
Also...
let me do something good before I die.
Are you okay?!
It's me.
Got the medical report?
You motherfucker!
Hey. easy. easy.
Sorry. friend.
It was tough. but we got a happy ending.
Your mom's surgery is
included in the $10 million.
It's better than robbing
a jewelry shop. no?
Are you listening to your own bullshit?!
Aren't you happy that a
fucker like him isn't your dad?
You fucker!
You thought I'd let you hit me again?
Throwing punches left and
right because you boxed a bit?
What the hell do you know?
What do you know!
Of course I do. moron.
I'm a Kopino too.
What?
What? What. man? Did you see?
If you did. stop being a drama queen.
What's with that look?
Forget it. let's just go.
If you got something to say.
say it on the way. we got a flight.
My fucking leg."
Not leaving?
Cops will be here soon.
go with your friend.
No wonder. no resemblance at all.
Blood never lies.
Hey! Don't ever come back!
Got that? You poor ass fucks.
She's calling you. answer her.
It hurts so much. fuck!
It hurts...
That bitch really did a number on my car.
I'm gonna get trypophobia looking at this.
Wait a minute. bullet holes
aren't covered by the insurance.
Can you get a move on?
You were so fast when running away.
It's gotta rain too?
You can drive. right?
My leg hurts too much to drive. you do it.
Put on your seat belt. asshole.
Can you drive well?
No. go a little further.
What are you doing?
Hey. hey. go easy.
You drive like a mofo. we can go now.
Who taught you to drive?
I heard the surgery went well.
Mr. Kim told me.
Oh yeah. will you continue
to look for your father in Korea?
Do you want my help?
You know I'm a professional!
I can give you a
special discount for the job...
Sorry.
Forget it.
Father or not. I'm so sick of Korea.
Very well.
But when you have some time.
go visit there...
Have you gone to the hospital?
I can't go to hospitals like that.
I got somewhere else.
Expensive. but he's a skilled doctor.
I feel better with these.
Stopped bleeding. and symptoms died down.
I just came to see your face one last time.
You won't see me even if you wanted to.
Now that you got some money.
live a happy life with your mom.
And stop boxing betting. got it?
My friend.
Friend. my ass.
Fuck...
"Fuck"? You said "fuck" to me?
I don't have a lot of time.
You cold-blooded bastard.
I really don't have a lot of time!
Wait for me. asshole!
It's strange.
I keep on gaining weight.
I always wanna eat. I sleep well...
Before. I did like what. 50 pull ups?
But now. I can easily do a hundred.
And everyone keeps telling me.
"You look better. you look healthy."
That's exactly what I'm saying...
There's nothing wrong with you.
Nothing at all. Absolutely healthy.
You are in great. great condition.
You obviously take good care of yourself.
Some people can experience similar things
when they stop smoking
after smoking a pack a day
for almost 10 years.
So this is...?
Vitamins.
Multi-vitamins.
They're good for you.
So in the future.
don't go to any illegal clinics
without permits.
It's not like medical licenses
can be bought.
What the fuck.
Do you want subtitles for any video?
-=[ ai.OpenSubtitles.com ]=-